{"1": {"question": "What is the chamber music for strings set work?", "correct": "1st movement from the String Quartet in G Major K.387 'Spring'", "incorrect": ["1st movement from the String Quartet in G Major K.378 'Summer'", "1st movement from the String Quintet in G Major K.387 'Spring'", "1st movement from the String Quartet in G Minor K.378 'Autumn'"]}, "2": {"question": "Who wrote the chamber music for strings set work?", "correct": "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart", "incorrect": ["Schubert", "Bach", "Beethoven"]}, "3": {"question": "What is the form of the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "Sonata form", "incorrect": ["Binary form", "Ternary form", "Rondo form"]}, "4": {"question": "What is the instrumentation of the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "2 violins, 1 viola, 1 cello", "incorrect": ["1 violin, 1 viola, 1 cello, 1 double bass", "3 violins, 1 viola", "2 violins, 2 violas"]}, "5": {"question": "How many movements are in the full piece of the Mozart?", "correct": "Four", "incorrect": ["Three", "Five", "Ten"]}, "6": {"question": "What key is the first movement in for the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "G major", "incorrect": ["D major", "G minor", "C major"]}, "7": {"question": "Briefly describe the phrasing in the Mozart first movement.", "correct": "The phrases are short and balanced (andecedent and consequent, or question and answer)", "incorrect": ["The phrases are long and smooth. Each phrase brings in a new idea.", "The phrases are unbalanced.", "The phrasing varies greatly, so there is no real way to define it."]}, "8": {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a compositional technique found in the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "Diatonic melodies", "incorrect": ["Recurring rhythmic motifs", "Imitation", "Chromaticism"]}, "9": {"question": "What is a string quartet?", "correct": "A genre of chamber music written for four string instruments", "incorrect": ["A genre of Baroque music written for four string instruments", "A subgenre of K-pop inspired by BTS written for four string instruments", "A genre of Classical music written for four orchestral instruments"]}, "10": {"question": "What separates mid-eighteenth century string quartets from Baroque forms?", "correct": "The lack of a basso continuo part", "incorrect": ["The lack of a second violin part", "The featuring of Jungkook", "Six movements in a quartet"]}, "11": {"question": "What kind of people did the string quartet appeal to?", "correct": "Eighteenth-century upper classes", "incorrect": ["Eighteenth-century working classes", "Nineteenth century upper classes", "BTS fangirls"]}, "12": {"question": "The string quartet was a ready form of private entertainment for whom?", "correct": "Wealthy individuals and families", "incorrect": ["Working-class individuals and families", "Bangtan Sonyeondan", "A large audience"]}, "13": {"question": "Why did composers manipulate conventions of string quartet form for their audiences?", "correct": "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper classes) enjoyed musical literacy and were educated on the form, so manipulating conventions surprised and delighted them.", "incorrect": ["Because President Namjoon asked them to", "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper and middle classes) enjoyed hearing the slight tweaks in convention, as it made it much more interesting for them to listen to.", "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper classes) did not enjoy hearing differences from convention, and the composers liked to annoy them."]}, "14": {"question": "How many string quartets are in the complete set of the Mozart?", "correct": "Six", "incorrect": ["Ten", "Five", "Four", "24?"]}, "15": {"question": "Who did Mozart dedicate the set of string quartets to?", "correct": "Haydn", "incorrect": ["Yoongi", "Purcell", "Bach"]}, "16": {"question": "Which of Haydn's quartets inspired Mozart to write his Haydn Quartets?", "correct": "Haydn's Op.33 set, which Mozart studied closely", "incorrect": ["Haydn's Op.44 set, which Mozart studied closely", "Haydn's Op.22 set, which Mozart studied closely", "Haydn's Op.55 set dedicated to Seokjin"]}, "17": {"question": "When did Haydn hear the quartets that Mozart dedicated to him?", "correct": "1785", "incorrect": ["1995", "1795", "1775"]}, "18": {"question": "What did Haydn say to the father Leopold when he was visiting from Salzburg?", "correct": "\"Before God, as an honest man, I tell you that your son is the greatest composer known to me either in person or by name. He has taste, and, what is more, the profound knowledge of composition.\"", "incorrect": ["\"BTS is the greatest band ever to form. Their music is wonderfully splendid and your son Wolfgang is quite a horrible composer compared to them.\"", "\"I very much dislike the quartets that your son wrote in my name. They do not reflect my compositions at all. Rather, they are written much more in your son's style than mine.\"", "\"Before God, as an honest man, your son will continue to be the great composer that he is and always has been. His quartets profoundly reflect mine with his own tasteful additions.\""]}, "19": {"question": "What is the Italian term used to indicate bowing on or near the bridge?", "correct": "Sul ponticello", "incorrect": ["Pizzicato", "Sul pontiv\u00c3\u00a9lla", "Bangtanio amazingo"]}, "20": {"question": "How many sections of violins are usually found in the symphony orchestra?", "correct": "Two", "incorrect": ["Three", "Four", "One"]}, "21": {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a way the Mozart is typical of the time period?", "correct": "Plays with formal conventions and expectations", "incorrect": ["Written in sonata form", "Uses Classical chamber music compositional techniques", "Development is in a related key"]}, "22": {"question": "What are the four movements of the complete Mozart?", "correct": "Fast movement, slow movement, minuet and trio, fast finale", "incorrect": ["Slow movement, minuet and trio, fast movement, fast finale", "There are three movements", "Minuet and trio, slow movement, fast movement, moderate finale"]}, "23": {"question": "Which is one of the expressive possibilities that the string quartet presented composers with?", "correct": "Greater subtleties than large-scale instrumental genres e.g. symphonies and concertos", "incorrect": ["Increased possibilities for tonal complexity, compared to large-scale instrumental genres", "Greater opportunities to feature J-Hope's rapping skills", "Less reliance on terrace dynamics, compared to solo works"]}, "24": {"question": "What is sonata form?", "correct": "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of three main sections: exposition, development and recapitulation.", "incorrect": ["A large-scale instrumental form consisting of three main sections: A, B, and A.", "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of two main sections: A and B.", "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of indefinite sections, in the order of A, B, A, C, A, D, A, E, et cetera."]}, "25": {"question": "Which of the following does the exposition NOT present?", "correct": "Tierce de Picardie", "incorrect": ["Thematic material", "Tonal contrast", "Modulating from the tonic to a related key (usually the dominant if the orgiinal key is major or the relative major if the original key is minor)"]}, "26": {"question": "Which of the following was NOT a composer of string quartets?", "correct": "John Dowland", "incorrect": ["Carl Dittersdorf", "Ludwig van Beethoven", "Johann Wanhal"]}, "27": {"question": "Mozart - What key does the piece modulate to for the development and what its relationship to the tonic key?", "correct": "D major, dominant", "incorrect": ["D major, subdominant", "E major, dominant", "B minor, relative minor"]}, "28": {"question": "Mozart - Which of the following is NOT part of the job of the development section?", "correct": "Repeat most of the exposition", "incorrect": ["Modulate through a range of keys", "Eventually go back to the tonic", "\"Work over\" motifs and thematic material of the exposition e.g. through sequenes and dominant harmony."]}, "29": {"question": "Mozart - Which of the following is used in the B section (minor)?", "correct": "Augmented chords", "incorrect": ["Diatonic melody", "Slower tempo (langsam)", "Modulation"]}, "30": {"question": "Mozart - What does the 'K' in K. 387 mean?", "correct": "The catalogue of Mozart's works made by Ludwig von Kochel", "incorrect": ["The catalogue of Mozart's works made by Kai Huening", "The catalogue of Baroque works made by Ludwig von Kochel", "The catalogue of all classical works made by Ludwig von Kochel"]}, "31": {"question": "Mozart - What does the '387' in K. 387 mean?", "correct": "It is his 387th work, ordering chronologically", "incorrect": ["It is his 87th work in his 3rd decade", "It is his 387th work, ordering alphabetically", "It is his 378th work, ordering chronologically"]}, "32": {"question": "What does the term Allegro vivace assai mean?", "correct": "Fast and very lively", "incorrect": ["Very fast and very lively", "Very fast", "Brisk and lively"]}, "33": {"question": "What is the lieder set work?", "correct": "Fruhlingstraum from Winterreise D. 911 by Schubert", "incorrect": ["Fruhlingstraum from Summerreise D.911 by Schubert", "Winterstraum from Fruhlingrreise D.911 by Schubert", "We Are Bulletproof : The Eternal by BTS (highly recommend)"]}, "34": {"question": "What does Fruhlingstraum mean?", "correct": "Dream of spring", "incorrect": ["Dream of summer", "Spring Day", "Dream of flowers"]}, "35": {"question": "What does Winterreise mean?", "correct": "Winter's journey", "incorrect": ["No More Dream", "Cold journey", "Lonely journey"]}, "36": {"question": "How many songs are in Winterreise and which number is Fruhlingstraum? (Respective)", "correct": "24, 11", "incorrect": ["14, 11", "34, 22", "24, 23"]}, "37": {"question": "What was a domestic factor in the development of the Romantic Lied?", "correct": "The growing availability and popularity of the piano and its presence in homes across a range of social classes.", "incorrect": ["The growing popularity of singing and availability of good teachers across a range of social classes.", "People's daughters transforming into ARMY fangirls, which led to composers panicking and introducing Romantic Lied.", "The decreasing popularity of Classical Lied among citizens which led composers to introduce Romantic Lied."]}, "38": {"question": "What was a factor in the development of Lied originally thought of by philosopher Johann Gottfried Herder?", "correct": "That language could unify all social classes, which sparked interest in lower classes.", "incorrect": ["That BTS would top the charts, so composers hurried to retain people's interest", "That music could unify all social classes, which sparked interest in lower classes.", "That language could only be appreciated by upper classes, which sparked an uprising in the lower classes."]}, "39": {"question": "Why did composers begin to focus on the piano accompaniment of Lieder?", "correct": "They realised the potential it had to support the text in a range of expressive ways.", "incorrect": ["They realised that it had previously had too great a role.", "They realised that BTS was too good at singing so they had to divert their attention to where they were not yet beaten.", "Their audiences were becoming dissatisfied with the piano part, so the composers had to adapt."]}, "40": {"question": "What is a song cycle?", "correct": "A unified collection of songs written to be performed in sequence.", "incorrect": ["A collection of songs written to be performed in a sequence of the performer's choice.", "A song with eleven unified parts to be performed in sequence. ", "A loop of the top ten BTS songs that plays ten times."]}, "41": {"question": "When was Winterreise composed?", "correct": "1828", "incorrect": ["1838", "1848", "1997"]}, "42": {"question": "Who wrote the poem Schubert set in Fruhlingstraum?", "correct": "Wilhelm Muller", "incorrect": ["Suga", "Wilfred Muller", "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe"]}, "43": {"question": "Schubert - What is a recurring idea in the text?", "correct": "The contrast between dreams and reality", "incorrect": ["The personalities of BTS members", "The contrast between love and loneliness", "The similarities between the narrator's past life and his dreams"]}, "44": {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a means through which composers unify song cycles?", "correct": "The songs are in the same time and key.", "incorrect": ["The songs are linked by explicit recollection of musical motifs between certain songs.", "There is often an implicit narrative thread.", "The songs are presented as musically independent numbers and the relationship is more implicit."]}, "45": {"question": "How does the changing music of Fruhlingstraum reflect its text?", "correct": "The 'happier' sections are symbolic of warmth and dreams, while the 'sadder' sections are symbolic of coldness and reality.", "incorrect": ["The slower sections are reflective of reminiscing dreams, while the faster sections reflect the poet's haste to focus on reality.", "The happier sections symbolise Schubert's love for Kpop, while the sadder sections convey Schubert's distaste for antis.", "The minor sections reflect the poet's old and harsh life, while the major sections reflect the great new life he has found."]}, "46": {"question": "What is the main subject matter of Winterreise?", "correct": "A poet who realises his destiny to always wander in solitude and perhaps never know love, companionship and rest.", "incorrect": ["A poet who must journey the world forever in search of something that does not exist.", "The hardships endured by BTS, which make international ARMYs sad because they can't help their oppas in Korea \u00f0\u0178\u02dc\u00a2", "A wandering shepherd who is lost and cannot find his way home to his loved ones."]}, "47": {"question": "Comment on how Schubert treats the piano accompaniment in Fruhlingstraum.", "correct": "It imitates not only concrete imagery but evokes a feeling far more powerful than the text could.", "incorrect": ["It creates implicit imagery and imitates the feeling created by the text", "It is barely heard as Schubert intended for the voice to be the prominent part.", "It is the prominent part, bringing out the main imagery and themes in the piece."]}, "48": {"question": "How has Schubert set the six stanzas of poetry used in Fruhlingstraum?", "correct": "ABCABC", "incorrect": ["ABBCBB", "AABCCB", "ABACAA"]}, "49": {"question": "How is the music in Fruhlingstraum used to assist the story in Section A?", "correct": "Section A adopts a direct, folk song-like style with the help of the siciliana pattern which is associated with pastoral themes. The piano consists of gently rolling chords.", "incorrect": ["Section A adopts a direct, folk-like style with the help of the melisma pattern, associated with beautiful and floral themes", "Section A adopts a direct, folk song-like style with the help of the napolitana pattern which is associated with pastoral themes. The piano consists of gently rolling chords.", "Section A adopts a direct, folk song-like style with the help of the florentine pattern which is associated with pastoral themes. The piano consists of gently rolling chords."]}, "50": {"question": "How is the music in Fruhlingstraum used to assist the story in Section B?", "correct": "The tempo increases and the mode switches to minor. The piano consists of short, sharp block chords. ", "incorrect": ["The tempo decreases and the mode switches to minor. The piano consists of sharp, chromatic chords.", "The tempo increases and the mode switches to minor. The piano consists of harsh and fast rolling chords.", "The tempo increases and the mode switches to minor. The piano consists of gentle block chords."]}, "51": {"question": "How many lieder did Schubert write?", "correct": "Over 600", "incorrect": ["Over 60", "Over 6000", "Over 2013"]}, "52": {"question": "Schubert - What are the metric qualities of the verse?", "correct": "It is written in iambic trimeter (unstressed-stressed-unstressed)", "incorrect": ["It is written in iambic pentameter (unstressed-stressed)", "It is written in iambic pentameter (stressed-unstressed)", "It is written in iambic trimeter (stressed-unstressed-stressed)"]}, "53": {"question": "How is the structure of Fruhlingstraum effective as a narrative?", "correct": "Quatrains A are about the poet's dreams. Quatrains B are about his sudden awakening to reality. Quatrains C evoke the poet's yearning to return to his dreams.", "incorrect": ["Quatrains A are about reality. Quatrains B are about his unpleasant dreams. Quatrains C evoe the poet's yearning to return to reality.", "Quatrains A are about the poet's dreams. Quatrains B are about his sudden awakening to reality. Quatrains C evoke the poet's haste to flee his dreams.", "Quatrains A are about the poet's "]}, "54": {"question": "Which of the following does Schubert NOT use to effectively contrast the three ideas in Fruhlingstraum?", "correct": "Changes of instrumentation and texture", "incorrect": ["Changes of style", "Changes of modality and key", "Changes of tempo and meter"]}, "55": {"question": "What is the role of the piano in Lieder?", "correct": "It is an accompaniment of equal prominence to the text that supports the ideas and feelings of the text in expressive ways.", "incorrect": ["It is the prominent part, overpowering the text and expressively creating the main feelings and ideas.", "It is an accompaniment of less importance than the text that has little musical value, occasionally chipping in.", "It is a part of equal prominence to the voice and it introduces all the themes while the voice supports the ideas and feelings."]}, "56": {"question": "Schubert - What does the siciliana pattern found in the 4-bar introduction NOT present?", "correct": "Images of mountainous landscapes", "incorrect": ["Pastoral themes", "Images of nature", "Folk-like musical 'image' to the audience"]}, "57": {"question": "Schubert - What is the intention of the iambic trimeter used in the text?", "correct": "To promote a folk-like simplicity and 'artlessness' to the text", "incorrect": ["To demote a folk-like simplicity and 'artlessness' to the text", "To promote a delicacy and 'artfulness' to the text", "To promote images of sophistication for the audience"]}, "58": {"question": "Schubert - What is the final foot in the first line of each pair?", "correct": "An amphibrach", "incorrect": ["An iamb", "A reptibrach", "A trimeter", "A nudibranch"]}, "59": {"question": "Schubert - Do the main points of stress remain constant in the text?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Yes except for one instance", "Only for one instance"]}, "60": {"question": "What is a melisma?", "correct": "A group of notes sung to one syllable", "incorrect": ["A kind of rhythm associated with folkish, pastoral themes", "A term used to describe singing one note per syllable", "A pair of notes sung to one syllable"]}, "61": {"question": "Schubert - How is the setting of the text?", "correct": "Typical of Lied: it is mostly syllabic and the rare melismas occupy no more than 2 notes", "incorrect": ["Typical of Lied: it is rarely syllabic and melismas are found abundantly", "Untypical of Lied: it is rarely syllabic and almost every syllable is a melisma", "Typical of Lied: it is all syllabic."]}, "62": {"question": "Schubert - Which of the following is not represented by the major sections?", "correct": "Wealth", "incorrect": ["Dreaming", "Spring/warmth", "Love"]}, "63": {"question": "Schubert - Which of the following is not represented by the minor sections?", "correct": "Poverty", "incorrect": ["Reality", "Winter/coldness", "Loneliness"]}, "64": {"question": "Schubert - How is the material written?", "correct": "Almost completely diatonic without modulation", "incorrect": ["Almost completely chromatic with much modulation", "Almost completely diatonic with much modulation", "Very well "]}, "65": {"question": "Schubert - How does the piano foreshadow the singer's line?", "correct": "In the four-bar introduction by playing the melody in RH", "incorrect": ["In the four-bar introduction by playing the melody in LH", "In the eight-bar introduction by playing the melody in RH", "In the ten-bar introduction by playing the melody in RH"]}, "66": {"question": "Schubert - What is/are the predominant key(s) of the song?", "correct": "F major and F minor", "incorrect": ["E flat major and E flat minor", "G major and G minor", "D major and D minor"]}, "67": {"question": "Schubert - Which of the following keys are not used as [at least] brief modulations?", "correct": "D minor", "incorrect": ["C minor", "B flat major", "E flat minor"]}, "68": {"question": "Schubert - What does the \"D\" in D.911 mean?", "correct": "The catalogue of Schubert's works made by Otto Deutsch", "incorrect": ["A form of cataloguing created by Ottoman Deutsch", "Dani :))", "The catalogue of Schubert's works made by Otto Dutch"]}, "69": {"question": "Schubert - What does the \"911\" in D.911 mean?", "correct": "It is his 911th work, ordering chronologically", "incorrect": ["Jet Fuel conspiracy theories.", "It is his 911th individual song/piece", "It is his 911th work, ordering alphabetically"]}, "70": {"question": "What does Schnell mean?", "correct": "Fast", "incorrect": ["Slow", "Very fast", "Not too fast"]}, "71": {"question": "What does Etwas bewegt mean?", "correct": "With some movement", "incorrect": ["With much movement", "With very little movement", "With no movement"]}, "72": {"question": "What does Langsam mean?", "correct": "Slow", "incorrect": ["Fast", "Not too slow", "Very slow"]}, "73": {"question": "Schubert - What keys were the song originally written in?", "correct": "A major and A minor", "incorrect": ["F major and F minor", "G major and G minor", "E flat major and E flat minor"]}, "74": {"question": "Schubert - Why was the song transposed?", "correct": "To suit a lower voice", "incorrect": ["To suit a higher voice", "Because they felt like it", "So it was more accessible to all voices"]}, "75": {"question": "Schubert - What is the meter of Stanzas A?", "correct": "06-Aug", "incorrect": ["02-Apr", "03-Aug", "03-Apr"]}, "76": {"question": "Schubert - What is the meter of Stanzas B?", "correct": "06-Aug", "incorrect": ["02-Apr", "03-Aug", "03-Apr"]}, "77": {"question": "Schubert - What is the meter of Stanzas C?", "correct": "02-Apr", "incorrect": ["06-Aug", "03-Aug", "03-Apr"]}, "78": {"question": "Schubert - What is the key of Stanzas A?", "correct": "F major", "incorrect": ["F minor", "E flat major", "G major"]}, "79": {"question": "Schubert - What is the key of Stanzas B?", "correct": "F minor", "incorrect": ["F major", "E flat minor", "E flat major"]}, "80": {"question": "Schubert - What is the key of Stanzas C?", "correct": "F major - F minor", "incorrect": ["E flat major - E flat minor", "G major - G minor"]}, "81": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the harmony of Stanzas A.", "correct": "Settled, diatonic, often using the tonic chord", "incorrect": ["Unsettled, chromatic, frequent key changes", "Sometimes irresolute (questioning)", "Settled, diatonic, rarely using the tonic chord"]}, "82": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the melodic style of Stanzas A.", "correct": "Flowing and carefree, often using the siciliana rhythm, with some rising leaps", "incorrect": ["Agitated repeated notes, rising semitones, wide leaps (mostly descending)", "Simple (mostly quavers, narrow pitch range) then sad (minor key, wider pitch range)", "Flowing and carefree, often using melismas, with few leaps"]}, "83": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the accompaniment of Stanzas A.", "correct": "Flowing broken chords in continuous triplet rhythm", "incorrect": ["Arpeggiated chords", "Throbbing chords and broken octaves", "Flowing block chords in continuous triplet rhythm"]}, "84": {"question": "How is Schubert's type of strophic form different from simple strophic form?", "correct": "Schubert uses the same music for each group of stanzas (1&4, 2&5, 3&6) rather than for every stanza", "incorrect": ["Schubert uses different music for each stanza", "Schubert uses the same music for each group of stanzas (1&2, 3&4, 5&6) rather than for every stanza", "Schubert uses the same music for each group of stanzas (1&2&3, 4&5&6) rather than for every stanza"]}, "85": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the harmony of Stanzas B.", "correct": "Unsettled, chromatic, frequent key changes", "incorrect": ["Settled, diatonic, often using the tonic chord", "Sometimes irresolute (questioning)", "Unsettled, chromatic, infrequent key changes"]}, "86": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the melodic style of Stanzas B.", "correct": "Agitated repeated notes, rising semitones, wide leaps (mostly descending)", "incorrect": ["Flowing and carefree, often using the siciliana rhythm, with some rising leaps", "Simple (mostly quavers, narrow pitch range) then sad (minor key, wider pitch range)", "Agitated repeated notes, rising semitones, narrow leaps (mostly descending)"]}, "87": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the accompaniment of Stanzas B.", "correct": "Throbbing chords and broken octaves", "incorrect": ["Arpeggiated chords", "Flowing broken chords in continuous triplet rhythm", "Detached block chords and octaves"]}, "88": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the harmony of Stanzas C.", "correct": "Sometimes irresolute (questioning)", "incorrect": ["Settled, diatonic, often using the tonic chord", "Unsettled, chromatic, frequent key changes", "Very resolute and unquestioning"]}, "89": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the melodic style of Stanzas C.", "correct": "Simple (mostly quavers, narrow pitch range) then sad (minor key, wider pitch range)", "incorrect": ["Agitated repeated notes, rising semitones, wide leaps (mostly descending)", "Flowing and carefree, often using the siciliana rhythm, with some rising leaps", "Sad (minor key, narrow pitch range) then simple (mostly quavers, wider pitch range)"]}, "90": {"question": "Schubert - Describe the accompaniment of Stanzas C.", "correct": "Arpeggiated chords", "incorrect": ["Flowing broken chords in continuous triplet rhythm", "Throbbing chords and broken octaves", "Block chords"]}, "91": {"question": "What is the art song set work?", "correct": "O Mistress Mine from Let Us Garlands Bring Op.18 ", "incorrect": ["O Mistress Mine from Garlands Let Us Take Op.81 ", "Airplane, Pt.2 by BTS (highly recommend)", "O Mistress Mine from Let Us Bring Garlands Op.28 "]}, "92": {"question": "Who wrote the text of Let Us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Hitman Bang", "Milton", "Coleridge"]}, "93": {"question": "How many separate texts does Let Us Garlands Bring set?", "correct": "Five", "incorrect": ["Thirteen", "Eight", "Eleven"]}, "94": {"question": "Which of the following was NOT a composer of art song?", "correct": "[lieder composer]", "incorrect": ["Ralph Vaughan Williams", "John Ireland", "Arnold Bax"]}, "95": {"question": "What is O Mistress Mine about?", "correct": "It is a light-hearted reflection on love and youth.", "incorrect": ["It is a deep reflection on love and the mortality of youth.", "It is a light-hearted reflection on being grateful for little things.", "It is about waiting for 00:00 when the day will be over"]}, "96": {"question": "What was the 'English musical Renaissance'?", "correct": "The period in which England freed themselves from foreign musical influences, to have begun writing in a distinctively national manner", "incorrect": ["The period in which England freed themselves from old national English music and changed their style.", "The period in which English composers competed against BTS as to who could write better songs, and BTS won.", "The period in which England was overwhelmed by foreign musical influences and lost their national musical style."]}, "97": {"question": "Who wrote the art song set work?", "correct": "Gerald Finzi", "incorrect": ["Franz Schubert", "George Friedric Handel", "Rapmon"]}, "98": {"question": "What is the rhyme scheme of each sextain in Let Us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "AABCCB", "incorrect": ["ABACDC", "AAABBB", "ABBCBB"]}, "99": {"question": "Finzi - How are the modulations in the piece used to reflect the ideas in the text?", "correct": "The piece is bouncy as the poet addresses the object of his affection, and becomes more reflective as the poet addresses the need to be joyful while still young.", "incorrect": ["The song is determined as the idea of surviving one more day is expressed, and is temporarily taken back a notch as though building up energy to explode. ", "The piece is more reflective as the poet addresses the object of his affection, and becomes bouncy as the poet addresses the need to be joyful while still young.", "The piece is slow and melancholy as the poet addresses the once-was object of his affection, and becomes reflective as he addresses the need to be joyful while still young."]}, "100": {"question": "Finzi - What does the text consist of?", "correct": "Two six-line stanzas or sextains", "incorrect": ["Three six-line stanzas or sextains", "Six four-line stanzas or quatrains", "Hobicore vibes"]}, "101": {"question": "What is the role of the piano in O Mistress Mine?", "correct": "It ", "incorrect": ["It accompanies the vocal part", "It is accompanied by the vocal part"]}, "102": {"question": "Which play is the text of Let Us Garlands Bring from?", "correct": "Twelfth Night by Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Twelfth Day by Shakespeare", "Ninth Night by Shakespeare", "Life Goes On by BTS"]}, "103": {"question": "Finzi - How is the vocal line?", "correct": "Simple and direct", "incorrect": ["Extravagant and indirect", "Excessively simple", "Straightfoward and monotonous"]}, "104": {"question": "Finzi - How is the text set?", "correct": "Syllabic and has a natural rhythm close to the declamation of the words.", "incorrect": ["Melismatic and has a rhythm not very close to the declamation of the words.", "Melismatic but has a natural rhythm close to the declamation of the words.", "Syllabic but has a rhythm not very close to the declamation of the words."]}, "105": {"question": "How does Finzi emphasise the point of the text?", "correct": "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the final line of each stanza", "incorrect": ["By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the final line of the piece", "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano of motifs throughout the piece", "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the first line of each stanza"]}, "106": {"question": "Finzi - What key does the harmony shift to at the final line of each stanza?", "correct": "The parallel minor", "incorrect": ["The dominant", "The relative minor", "The parallel major"]}, "107": {"question": "Finzi - What is the form of the song?", "correct": "Semi-strophic", "incorrect": ["Modified strophic", "Simple strophic", "Binary"]}, "108": {"question": "Finzi - What are the stanzas framed by?", "correct": "A piano inroduction, interlude and postlude", "incorrect": ["A piano introduction, interlude and voice+piano postlude", "A voice+piano introduction, interlude and postlude", "A voice introduction, voice+piano interlude, voice postlude"]}, "109": {"question": "Finzi - What key is the piece in?", "correct": "E flat major", "incorrect": ["A flat major", "E major", "F major"]}, "110": {"question": "What key does O Mistress Mine modulate to?", "correct": "It does not modulate", "incorrect": ["C minor", "The parallel minor", "G minor"]}, "111": {"question": "Finzi - How is the melody written?", "correct": "Mostly diatonic except for the end of each stanza where a modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["Mostly chromatic except for the end of each stanza where it becomes diatonic", "All diatonic", "Mostly diatonic except for the end of the piece where a modal mixture is introduced"]}, "112": {"question": "Finzi - What is the mood of the piece?", "correct": "Light-hearted and jaunty but becomes more reflective as modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["Reflective but becomes more light-hearted and jaunty as modal mixture is introduced", "Light-hearted and jaunty", "Reflective"]}, "113": {"question": "Which syllables does Finzi ensure land on the first beat of the bar?", "correct": "Stressed", "incorrect": ["Unstressed", "Both", "jUst rAndOm syLLaBLeS"]}, "114": {"question": "Finzi - Where are the only instances of direct imitation found?", "correct": "At the end of each stanza between the voice and the piano", "incorrect": ["At the beginning of each stanza between the voice and the piano", "There are no instances of direct imitation in the piece", "At the end of the piece between the voice and the piano"]}, "115": {"question": "Finzi - Describe the texture of the accompaniment at the end of the each stanza.", "correct": "Legato articulation and longer note values, slower pace, and dramatic contrast of dynamics.", "incorrect": ["Staccato articulation and shorter note values, faster pace, no contrast of dynamics.", "Legato articulation and longer note values, slower pace, less contrast of dynamics.", "Legato articulation and shorter note values, slower pace and dramatic contrast of dynamics."]}, "116": {"question": "Finzi - Describe the cadence at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "It is joined with the commencement of the next piano section (interlude/postlude)", "incorrect": ["It is separated from the next piano section (interlude/postlude)", "It is joined with the commencement of the next stanza", "It is joined with a four-bar outro of sorts before the interlude/postlude commences"]}, "117": {"question": "Finzi - In what way is the piece flexible and natural?", "correct": "The voice sets the text differently in each stanza while the accompaniment stays the same.", "incorrect": ["The accompaniment is different in each stanza while the voice stays the same.", "The voice sets the text differently in each stanza, just like the accompaniment.", "The voice and accompaniment stay the same, but rubato and ornaments are used."]}, "118": {"question": "Generally, what is the role of the Piano in Art songs?", "correct": "Shares prominence with the vocal part", "incorrect": ["Secondary to the vocal part", "Ternary to the vocal part", "Primary above the vocal part", "Quaternary to the vocal part"]}, "119": {"question": "Let us garlands bring is a set of how many songs?", "correct": "Five", "incorrect": ["Thirteen", "Eight", "Eleven"]}, "120": {"question": "What does Allegretto amabile mean?", "correct": "Moderately fast and pleasant", "incorrect": ["Not too fast and pleasant", "Very fast and unpleasant", "Walking pace and pleasant"]}, "121": {"question": "Finzi - Which of the following is NOT a stylistic characteristic of the song?", "correct": "Use of raised 7th notes in minor keys", "incorrect": ["Some dissonance and occasional use of parallel 5ths to the bass", "Irregular phrase lengths and syncopation and changes of meter", "Angular melodies (at times)"]}, "122": {"question": "What does sempre staccato mean?", "correct": "Always detached", "incorrect": ["Never detached", "The Ravenswood magazine", "Very detached"]}, "123": {"question": "Finzi - What key is the piano part in?", "correct": "E flat major", "incorrect": ["E flat minor", "A major", "A minor"]}, "124": {"question": "Which of the following techniques does Finzi NOT use in the song?", "correct": "Chromatic harmony", "incorrect": ["Imitation", "Counterpoint", "Diatonic harmony"]}, "125": {"question": "What kind of techniques does Finzi deliberately use in the song?", "correct": "Techniques associated with earlier music styles from Shakespeare's time", "incorrect": ["Techniques ahead of Finzi's time", "Techniques associated with earlier styles such as Classical", "Techniques associated with Kpop"]}, "126": {"question": "Finzi - What is the underlying message of the song?", "correct": "To seize life's joys and pleasures while you can", "incorrect": ["To be yourself", "To pursue your dreams", "To listen to BTS"]}, "127": {"question": "Finzi - Which of the following is NOT part of the change in texture at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "Faster", "incorrect": ["Broader", "Denser", "Slower"]}, "128": {"question": "Finzi - Who is the piece sung by?", "correct": "Feste, the jester in the court of Countess Olivia", "incorrect": ["Countess Olivia, to her jester, Feste", "Feste, the brother of Countess Olivia", "Feste, the father of Countess Olivia"]}}